Samaya. Come in. Yes, come in. Thank you.
Good morning, sir. Good morning. Good morning, ma'am. Take a
seat. A chad. Thank you, sir.
Akshad Jain. Yes, sir. Give you a brief description
about yourself. So, my name is Aksha Jain. I am 23
years old. I was born in Jaipur, Rajasthan, from where I've done my high schooling.
And I done my bachelor's in design from IIT Guwahati.
And so my interests include fitness, swimming, football.
And so this is going to be my second attempt at UPSC and
my first interview. We're going through your detailed
application form, sir. And we have come to know that both your
parents are already civil servants. Yes, sir. They are in the police
service or, sir, my father is in the police service. My mother
is in the revenue service. She is in the rain.